[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Who created Flutter?",
        "options": [
            "Facebook",
            "Adobe",
            "Google",
            "Microsoft"
        ],
        "answer": "Google"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What is Flutter?",
        "options": [
            "Android Development Kit",
            "IOS Development Kit",
            "Web Development Kit",
            "SDK to build beautiful IOS, Android, Web & Desktop Native Apps"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which programing language is used by Flutter",
        "options": [
            "Ruby",
            "Dart",
            "C++",
            "Kotlin"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "How many programming languages are in use?",
        "options": [
            "20",
            "50",
            "2000",
            "5000"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Who founded Apple Computer?",
        "options": [
            "Steve Jobs",
            "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "Bill Gates",
            "Sundar Pichai"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which of these is not a peripheral, in computer terms?",
        "options": [
            "Keyboard",
            "Mouse",
            "Motherboard",
            "Monitor"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which of these is not a peripheral, in computer terms?",
        "options": [
            "Keyboard",
            "Mouse",
            "Motherboard",
            "Monitor"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "A network designed to allow communication within an organization is called:",
        "options": [
            "the Internet",
            "the Intranet",
            "a browser",
            "the World Wide Web"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Who created Dart programing language?",
        "options": [
            "Lars Bak and Kasper Lund",
            "Brendan Eich",
            "Bjarne Stroustrup",
            "Jeremy Ashkenas"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Is Flutter for Desktop stable?",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Is Flutter for Web stable?",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    }
]